Bunny and the Bull is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Paul King.
A young shut-in takes an imaginary road trip inside his apartment, based on
mementos and memories of a European trek from years before.
Stephen, played by Edward Hogg.
Bunny, played by Simon Farnaby.
Eloisa, played by Verónica Echegui.
Atilla, played by Julian Barratt.
Javier, played by Noel Fielding.
Museum Curator, played by Richard Ayoade.
Bunny and the Bull is a 2009 British comedy film
written and directed by Paul King.
It stars Edward Hogg and Simon Farnaby in a surreal recreation of a road trip.
King has previously worked on British television comedies The Mighty Boosh and Garth Marenghi's Darkplace;
the film is made in a similar style and has cameo appearances from stars of those series.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.